<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 days recipe</string>
    <string name="app_title">30 days recipe</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1: ADOBO</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2: Bangus Belly</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3: Bicol Express</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4: Bistek Tagalog</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5: Chicken Tinola </string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6: Chicken Afritada</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7: Crispy Pata </string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8: Dinuguan </string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9: Ginataang Manok </string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10: Ginataang Sitaw at Kalabasa </string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11: Tortang Talong</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12: Ginataang Langka</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13: Pinakbet</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14: Chicken Afritada</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15: Pancit Malabon</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16: Tinolang Tahong</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17: Gising-Gising</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18: Tortang Talong with Giniling</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19: Bicol Express</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20: Pork Sinigang</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21: Laing</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22: Adobong Pusit</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23: Pancit Bihon Guisado</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24: Lechon Paksiw</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25: Tinumok</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26: Pinaupong Manok</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27: Crispy Pata</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28: Sisig</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29: Ginataang Manok</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30: Dinuguan</string>

    <string name="description1">Ingredients:
        1 kg chicken (cut into serving pieces) or pork belly (cut into cubes)
        1/2 cup soy sauce
        1/2 cup vinegar (cane or coconut vinegar works well)
        1 head garlic (minced)
        1 onion (sliced)
        3-4 pieces dried bay leaves
        1 teaspoon whole peppercorns
        1 cup water
        2 tablespoons cooking oil
        Salt (to taste)
        Sugar (optional, to balance the flavors)
        Instructions:
        In a bowl, marinate the chicken or pork in soy sauce, vinegar, minced garlic, and peppercorns for at least 30 minutes (overnight marination is even better for deeper flavors).
        Heat the cooking oil in a pan over medium heat. Once hot, add the marinated meat (reserve the marinade) and brown it on all sides.
        Add the sliced onion and sauté until translucent.
        Pour in the marinade and add the dried bay leaves. Bring to a boil.
        Once boiling, lower the heat, cover the pan, and let it simmer for about 30-40 minutes or until the meat is tender. Stir occasionally to ensure even cooking.
        Add water if needed, depending on how much sauce you want.
        Season with salt to taste. If the sauce is too tangy for your liking, you can add a bit of sugar to balance the flavors.
        Serve hot with steamed rice.
</string>
    <string name="description2">
        Ingredients:
500g shrimp (head-on for more flavor, peeled and deveined)
1 medium-sized onion (quartered)
2 medium-sized tomatoes (quartered)
1 radish (sliced)
1 eggplant (sliced)
1 bunch of kangkong (water spinach), or any leafy greens like spinach or bok choy
1 packet (40g) sinigang mix (available in Filipino/Asian stores)
1 liter water
Fish sauce or salt (to taste)
Freshly ground black pepper (to taste)
Instructions:
In a pot, bring the water to a boil.
Add the onions and tomatoes. Let it simmer for a few minutes until the tomatoes start to soften and release their juices.
Add the radish and eggplant. Simmer until they start to soften.
Add the sinigang mix and stir to dissolve it into the broth.
Add the shrimp and cook until they turn pink and opaque.
Add the kangkong or leafy greens and cook for another minute until wilted.
Season with fish sauce or salt and freshly ground black pepper to taste.
Serve hot with steamed rice.

    </string>
    <string name="description3"> IT skills improve with practice, so code, troubleshoot, and experiment regularly.</string>
    <string name="description4"> Engage with online and offline communities to connect with fellow students and professionals.</string>
    <string name="description5"> Build a professional network early on by attending events, joining LinkedIn, and connecting with classmates.</string>
    <string name="description6"> The ability to troubleshoot issues is crucial in IT. Develop problem-solving skills.</string>
    <string name="description7"> IT projects can be time-consuming. Learn effective time management to handle assignments and projects.</string>
    <string name="description8"> Follow industry news, blogs, and forums to stay updated on the latest trends and technologies.</string>
    <string name="description9"> Learn about the importance of cybersecurity and best practices for keeping systems secure.</string>
    <string name="description10">Knowing how to search effectively is a valuable skill in IT. Learn to use Google and other resources efficiently.</string>
    <string name="description11">Practice documenting your work. Good documentation is crucial for collaboration and troubleshooting.</string>
    <string name="description12">Set up your own projects, experiment with software, and get hands-on experience beyond the classroom.</string>
    <string name="description13">Understand how version control systems like Git work. Its essential for collaborative coding.</string>
    <string name="description14">IT is broad. Explore different specializations like software development, network administration, or data science. </string>
    <string name="description15">Join hackathons and coding competitions to enhance your problem-solving skills.
</string>
    <string name="description16">Showcase your projects and skills through a personal portfolio. It can be a great asset when job hunting.</string>
    <string name="description17">Develop communication and teamwork skills. IT projects often involve collaboration.
</string>
    <string name="description18">Understand the ethical considerations in IT, especially when dealing with sensitive data and systems.</string>
    <string name="description19">Look for internships or co-op programs to gain real-world experience.</string>
    <string name="description20">Dont hesitate to ask questions. Its better to clarify doubts early on.</string>
    <string name="description21">Contribute to open source projects to collaborate with experienced developers and enhance your skills.</string>
    <string name="description22">Understand Agile methodologies commonly used in IT project management.
</string>
    <string name="description23">Embrace the mindset of continuous learning. The IT field evolves rapidly, and ongoing education is key.</string>
    <string name="description24">Use tools like project management software and planners to stay organized, especially when juggling multiple tasks.</string>
    <string name="description25">Develop communication, teamwork, and presentation skills alongside technical skills.</string>
    <string name="description26">Set up a home lab to experiment with different technologies in a controlled environment.</string>
    <string name="description27">Supplement your school curriculum with online courses and tutorials to delve deeper into specific topics.</string>
    <string name="description28">Regularly back up your projects and important files to avoid data loss.</string>
    <string name="description29">IT can be challenging. Learn to cope with setbacks, learn from failures, and bounce back stronger.</string>
    <string name="description30">Enjoy what youre learning. Passion for the field will make your journey more fulfilling.</string>
</resources>
